

AHMAD **KARIEM**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



Phone



Email



Website



Address

187 Cottonwood Dr. Sunset Estates, SK.



EDUCATION





University of

2011 - 2015 **Bachelor of Science Honors - Biochemistry**

> University of Saskatchewan



ABOUT ME

I am a 100% self-taught full-stack developer from Saskatoon Saskatchewan. After several years of professional experience working in areas such as tech sales, marketing, and data analysis, I decided to pursue a field that has always interested me - computer programming.



WORK EXPERIENCE



Data Analyst **Red Wireless**

2021 - 2022

- Managing the collection, upkeep, and analysis of company data
- Automating processes using Zapier
- Managing freelance developers and designers



SkipTheDishes

2020-2021

Territory Sales Executive

- · Prospecting, pitching and signing new restaurant partners across Saskatchewan
- · Advising new restaurant partners on best practices to succeed on Skip



Vendasta

2019 - 2020

BDR/SDR Team Lead/SDR

- As a BDR prospecting, pitching and signing new channel partners
- As SDR Team Lead Managed a team of 5 SDRs while maintaining a full SDR quota
- As an SDR Sales prospecting and connecting prospects with the BDR team



MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

HTML/CSS JavaScript React ExpressJS NodeJS PostgreSQL



MY REFERENCES

Available upon request